Hi, choosing make-up colors is something that many women have problems with.
I'm going to help you find the best make-up colors that will work for you.
My name is Sylvia Russell and this is how you can choose the best make-up colors.
Now, make-up color really depends on you, what you like and what you don't like.
If you stick with what you like, normally you'll come out on top.
Now remember as we age, we need to modify the colors that we wear.
We want to wear less blacks, and dark colors, using lighter browns and mauves.
Making sure that the color we choose compliments the skin tone.
As you can see our model here has beautiful cheek bones, beautiful lips, so we wanted to enhance those things.
We use a nice, peachy color on the cheeks, nothing too red, and a very nice color, almost the same color as her lips, just to give her a little extra pop.
Now, when you're doing your eyes, using a dark liner is o.k, we just want to make sure that it's complimented and it's very even.
We don't want anything too harsh, and too dark.
So, making sure that the entire face is balanced is very important.
There are many colors to choose from, and remember if you stick to the things that you like, you're normally going to do very well.
Make sure to play with different colors, and make sure that you have someone near you that can give you an honest opinion about what looks good on you.
My name is Sylvia Russell and this is how you can choose make-up colors.